I believe in the Church of Baseball.
我的宗教信仰就是棒球
I've tried all the major religions and most of the minor ones.
曾经我也信仰过世界上 大部分的大小宗教
I've worshipped Buddha, Allah, Brahma, Vishnu...
我崇拜过释迦摩尼， 真主安拉，梵天，毗湿奴
Siva, trees, mushrooms and Isadora Duncan.
湿婆神，树精草怪，还有邓肯
I know things.
然后我学到了些道理
For instance, there are 108 beads in a Catholic rosary...
比如说， 玫瑰经念珠上有108颗珠子
and there are 108 stitches in a baseball.
而任何一个棒球上都缝有108针
When I learned that, I gaveJesus a chance.
当我明白了这些， 我也给过耶酥机会
But it just didn't work out between us.
可看来我们的脾气实在是不和
The Lord laid too much guilt on me.
我对无止尽的赎罪没什么兴趣
I prefer metaphysics to theology.
比起神学，我更喜欢形而上学
You see, there's no guilt in baseball...
你想，棒球不需要人赎罪
and it's never boring...
也永远不会使人厌烦
which makes it like sex.
就象是性爱一样
There's never been a ballplayer who slept with me...
和我睡过觉的球手
who didn't have the best year of his career.
全都在当年达到了 棒球生涯的巅峰
Making love is like hitting a baseball...
做爱就象是挥杆击球--
you just gotta relax and concentrate.
你同样需要放松精神 和集中注意力
Besides, I'd never sleep with a player hitting under.250...
此外，我从不和安打数 低于250的人上床
unless he had a lot of RBI's or was a great glove man up the middle.
除非他拥有极高的打点 或者他是优秀的中场接球手
You see, there's a certain amount of life wisdom I give these boys.
我让这些男孩们获得了人生的体验
I can expand their minds.
这让他们变的聪明
Sometimes when I've got a ballplayer alone...
有时候当我和某个球员独处
I'll just read Emily Dickinson or Walt Whitman to him.
我会给他念艾米莉和惠特曼的诗
And the guys are so sweet, they always stay and listen.
那些家伙可爱极了， 他们总会静下来倾听
Of course, a guy will listen to anything if he thinks it's foreplay.
当然，只要男人认为是性爱的前奏， 都会很认真的去听
I make them feel confident, and they make me feel safe...
我让他们获得自信， 而他们给我安全感…
and pretty.
还有美丽
Of course, what I give them lasts a lifetime.
我给了他们生命中最美好的时间
What they give me lasts 142 games.
而他们让我白看了142场比赛
Sometimes it seems like a bad trade...
有时候这交易看来并不合算
but bad trades is a part of baseball.
可这也是为了棒球
Who can forget Frank Robinson for Milt Pappas, for God's sake?
谁又能忘记弗兰克罗宾逊 为缪特巴帕斯做出的帮助
It's a long season, and you gotta trust it.
赛季还很长，你总该抱有希望
I've tried 'em all, I really have.
我试过所有的信仰， 真的全试过
And the only church that truly feeds the soul...
但只有一种真正留在心中--
day in, day out... is the Church of Baseball.
无论时光怎么流逝-- 那就是对棒球的狂热
Hey, Skip, that Max, hell of a guy.
领队，麦克斯这家伙真叫人受不了
Where's Ebby?
艾比在哪儿？
Ain't he warming up yet?
他还没热身吗？
No. His professional debut tonight, and he forgets about it.
没有，这是他职业生涯的初赛 而他居然忘记了
Better find our "bonus baby."
最好去找找我们的"胜利宝贝"吧
Have you seen Ebby?
看到艾比吗？
No.
没有
Ebby!
艾比！
Jesus.
天
Game starts in four minutes. Why ain't you warm?
比赛再过四分钟就开始了 你怎么还不去热身
I am warm.
我是在热身
Jesus, this is your professional debut tonight.
今天是你在职业联赛的初赛
Million guys give their left nut to be in your shoes.
成百万的人烧坏了脑子 花钱买票只为看你打球
You're leaving your fastball in the locker room for some piece of ass.
而你却在紧要关头还在 衣帽间里和不三不四的女人鬼混
Skip, it is me.
领队，是我
I am not some, quote, piece of ass, unquote.
我不是那种"不三不四的女人"
Oh, Millie.
哦，米莉
Jeez, sorry. Didn't recognize you.
抱歉，没认出是你
Don't take this personally, Millie, but if I catch you in here again...
但别以为我是在开玩笑， 米莉，要是再让我在这儿逮到你…
you're banned from the ballpark.
从此你就别想踏进棒球场一步
You can't ban me from the ballpark...
你不能禁止我来这里
'cause my daddy donated that scoreboard.
球场上的积分板还是我爸爸捐赠的
And if you ban me, he just might take that scoreboard away.
要是你禁止我来， 他立马会把记分板给你拆走
What do we need a scoreboard for?
我们要记分板有个屁用？
We ain't scored any runs all year.
整一年我们都没得什么分
Now you get your ass out there!
快给我滚出来！
Hey, boss, I got a question.
老板，我有个问题
What?
什么？
You think I need a nickname? I think I need a nickname.
你觉得我该起个绰号吗？ 我觉得有需要
We were talking about it. All the great ones have nicknames.
我们都讨论过了 所有优秀的球员都有绰号
Like "Oil Can," "Catfish." What was the one you were...
比如说"油罐"啦，"猫鱼"啦 你刚说的是什么来着--
"Pokey."
"波奇小子"
What do you think of"Pokey"?
觉得这如何？
You got three minutes.
你还有三分钟
Goddamn, son of a bitchin', motherfuckin' shithead!
混蛋，真是脑袋里面进了水！
Time for another quickie.
还有时间再做一次
Jesus, you got a game to pitch.
天啊，你还得比赛呢
We got three minutes.
还有三分钟
Come on, folks. Let's hear it for Max Patkin...
大伙来吧，让我们为麦克斯鼓掌--
the clown prince of baseball.
他是最可爱的棒球小丑
You gonna sit there all day?
还要坐到什么时候？上场了
And now "The Greatest Show on Dirt"...
好戏就要开演了
your own Durham Bulls!
达勒姆公牛队队员出场！
I'm there. I'm ready.
我来了，我准备好了
And now WRDU radio presents...
现在是北卡罗来纳电台 的泰迪格兰德
the voice of the Durham Bulls, Teddy Garland.
为您现场解说达勒姆公牛队比赛实况
The Bulls off to a slow start, having dropped their first three games.
本赛季公牛队出师不利， 已经输掉了头三场比赛
But hope to turn it around tonight with the professional debut...
但扭转连败局面的希望被寄托在
of heralded young pitcher, Ebby Calvin LaLoosh.
年轻投手艾比卡尔文拉路什 的初次登场上
Millie, you gotta stay out of the clubhouse.
米莉，你不该去休息室的
You're gonna get everybody in trouble.
现在可能会给大家都带来麻烦
I got lured.
我是被勾引的
You did not get lured. Women do not get lured.
你没有被勾引， 女人是不会被勾引的
They are too strong and powerful for that. Now say it...
你有能力也有意志抵抗诱惑， 现在跟着我说…
"I did not get lured. I accept full responsibility for my actions."
"我不是被勾引的， 我会对我的行为负全责"
That's better. You got your radar ready?
现在好点了，测试仪准备好了吗？
- Ready. - Go to it.
-准备好了 -那快就位
Steppin' in for the Peninsula White Sox...
半岛白袜队一番击球手…
is leadoff hitter Willie Foster.
威利福斯特出场
Word on LaLoosh is that the good-looking, young pitcher...
拉路什是位英俊，年轻的投球手
has a major-league fastball, but sometimes has problems with control.
拿手技是一流的快球， 可惜状态不太稳定
Damn.
好家伙
One ball, no strikes to Willie Foster.
一坏，没有好球
No problem!
没关系！
Go get 'em, one, two, three, babe. Get 'em, big guy.
加油，一，二，三，宝贝
Ninety-five miles an hour.
时速九十五英里
That's great. He looks just great.
太棒了，他正在状态
Stepping in for the Peninsula White Sox...
半岛白袜队保送上垒
second baseman Allen Powley.
下一棒艾伦波利出场
What's it say?
怎么会这样？
It says he's not bending his back on his follow-through.
结束动作时他没有弯背
Scotty, baby, take this to Ebby Calvin.
斯科特，把这交给艾比卡尔文
All right, let's get down to it. How was Ebby Calvin LaLoosh?
好吧，让我们来好好瞧瞧 艾比卡尔文是何方神圣？
Well, he fucks like he pitches.
他的投球就和做爱时一个样
Sort of all over the place.
搞的乱七八糟的
My!
天！
He walked 18.
18次保送上垒
A new league record.
联赛的新记录
- Struck out 18. - Another new league record.
-18次三振出局 -又是一个联赛新记录
In addition, he hit the sportswriter...
此外，他还击中体育记者…
the public address announcer, the Bull mascot twice.
击中现场解说， 还击中吉祥牛两次
Also, new league records.
这也是联赛新记录
But, Joe...
不过话说回来，乔…
this guy's got some serious shit.
这家伙还真有一手
Yeah, serious shit.
是有一手
Who are you? Who's he?
你是谁？ 他是谁？
I'm "the player to be named later."
我是"你会记得的球员"
Crash Davis? I'm Joe Riggins.
克拉舍戴维斯吗？ 我是乔瑞金斯
And you, Larry Hockett, should recognize me...
而你，拉里霍克特， 你应该认识我…
'cause five years ago in the Texas League...
因为五年前在德州联盟赛中…
you were pitching for El Paso, I was hitting cleanup for Shreveport.
你担任埃尔帕索队的投手 而我为什里夫波特队效力
You hung a curveball on an 0-2 pitch in a 3-2 game...
第三节的关键时刻 你投了个曲线球
in the bottom of the eighth, and I tattooed it...
结果球路被我看破
over the Michelin Tire sign, beat you 4-3.
我将球高高的击出了场外
I remember. I should have thrown a slider.
我记得，我该投外旋下坠球的
Damn, Crash, how ya doin?
克拉舍，最近还好吗？
I'm too old for this shit.
我已经太老了
Why in the hell am I back in A ball?
为什么还要召我回来比赛？
'Cause of Ebby Calvin LaLoosh.
因为艾比卡尔文拉路什
Big club's got a hundred grand in him.
俱乐部很看重他
He's got a million-dollar arm with a five-cent head.
他有着价值百万的金手臂 但可惜没什么头脑
Had a gun on him tonight.
看看他今晚的表现吧
Last five pitches he threw were faster than the first five.
最后五球的球速 居然超过了最先的五球
He's got the best young arm I've seen in 30 years.
他有着我三十年来 所见最棒的手臂
You've been around.
你已经到周围看过了
You're smart. You're a professional.
你够聪明，也够专业
We want you to mature the kid.
我们想要你使这孩子成熟起来
We want you to room with him on the road.
我们想要你指引他上路
Stay on his case all year. He can go all the way.
只需要带他一年， 他就完全独立了
Yeah? Where can I go?
是吗？那我干些什么？
You can keep going to the ballpark...
你会继续在球场上打球
keep getting paid to do it.
我们会因此而付你钱
Beats the hell out of working at Sears.
给那些无聊的百货公司 上班族打些好球看看
Sears sucks. I once worked there. Sold Lady Kenmores.
该死的百货公司，我也干过那种活
Nasty work.
真是令人厌恶的工作
Even if it is the Carolina League...
此外既然这是加州联盟…
this is a chance to play every day.
你还有机会每天都打球
You don't want a player. You want a stable pony.
你要的不是球员，你只想要训马师
No.
不是的
My triple A contract gets bought out...
要是我签下这三年合约
so I can hold the flavor of the month's dick.
只是为了围着那家伙转
Is that it? Fuck this fucking game!
难道不是吗？ 去他妈的比赛吧！
I fuckin' quit, all right?
我不干，好吗？
Who we play tomorrow?
明天的对手是谁？
Winston-Salem. Batting practice, 11:30.
温斯顿赛伦队， 练习赛，11：30开始
How's it feel to get your first professional win?
赢得了职业联赛的第一场胜利 你有何感想？
It feels out there. It's a major rush.
这感觉很轻松， 我的目标是全国联赛
It doesn't just feel out there, it feels out there.
这其实也不是完全很轻松， 但就是很轻松
Kind of radical in a kind of tubular way.
就象是从管道里被激发出来
But most of all, it's out there.
但总的来说就是很轻松
This is hopeless. This is utterly, fucking hopeless.
无可救药.根本是无可救药
Hey, I'm Millie.
嘿，我是米莉
I'm Tony. I play second base.
我叫托尼，是二垒手
I know.
我知道
How do you just keep coming back every year?
为什么每年都回来？
'Cause I love the game, Annie. I love it.
因为我爱这运动，安妮 我爱它
- Here you go. - We didn't order these.
-给你们 -我们并没有点这些
- He did. - Who?
-是他点的 -谁？
The guy in the booth.
角落里那家伙
Who's that?
那是谁？
That's Crash Davis. Hey, Crash, come here.
那是克拉舍戴维斯 嗨，克拉舍，过来
Get over here.
快过来
He's kinda cute.
他看来很可爱
He's played in more ballparks than I have.
他打过的球赛比我看过的还多
Hell of a guy.
是个厉害的家伙
He's really different.
完全的与众不同
I actually saw him read a book without pictures once.
我曾看见他在读全是文字的书
- Hi, Max. - How you doing?
-你好，麦克斯 -你好吗？
Come over and sit down.
快过来坐下
I'm Crash.
我是克拉舍
Annie Savoy. Wanna dance?
安妮苏文，想跳舞吗？
I don't dance.
我不会跳
How embarrassing.
真扫兴
What is that?
快瞧啊
Who's he dancing with?
他这是和谁在跳啊？
All of them, I think.
我想是所有人
You Annie Savoy?
你是安妮苏文吗？
Thanks for your note. You're right. I wasn't bending my back.
谢谢你的提醒 你说的对，我是没有弯背
You have a live arm there.
你表现的很不错
Thanks.
谢谢
Ebby Calvin LaLoosh.
艾比卡尔文拉路什
You need a nickname, honey.
你需要起个绰号，亲爱的
I've been telling everybody that.
我和谁都这么说
- You wanna dance? - Yeah.
-想跳舞吗？ -好啊
She's dancing with me.
她正准备和我跳呢
'Fraid not, pal.
恐怕不行，朋友
You boys gonna fight over little ol' me?
你们想要为争我打架吗？
- No. - Let's go.
-算了 -过来
Step outside and party, man.
有种到外面去好好谈谈
Don't be such guys.
别那么无聊
Max, let's dance.
麦克斯，我们来跳
You comin' or not, homeboy?
到底来不来，软脚虾？
Let's go. Come on. We're waitin'.
来啊，过来 我们等了好一会了
- Let's go, homeboy. - Come on, Ebby. There he is.
-出来啊，懦夫 -行了，艾比.他来了
I don't believe in fighting. Let's just...
我不信打架能解决问题 让我们--
That's really sweet. Fuck you, you pussy.
说的多动听啊，去死吧，娘娘腔
All right. Take the first shot at me.
好，那么放马过来吧
No way. I don't hit no man first.
不行，我从不先动手
All right, then.
那么好吧
Hit me in the chest with that.
朝我胸前扔过来
I'd kill you.
这会要了你的命的
From what I hear, you couldn't hit water...
我倒是觉的， 你连自己怎么死的都不知道…
if you fell out of a fuckin' boat.
就别先在这儿胡说了
Go ahead, man.
那么好吧，伙计
Go ahead, come on. Right in the chest.
来吧，对准胸口
- No way. - Come on, Meat.
-不行 -来啊，废物
You're not gonna hit me 'cause you're thinking about it already.
你不敢用那球扔我 是因为你已经想到了结果
Starting to think how embarrassing it would be...
你知道要是投不中我， 反而误中了其他人
to miss in front of these people, how somebody might laugh.
有人嘲笑你时，会有多尴尬
Come on, Rook. Show us that million-dollar arm...
快来啊，让我们瞧瞧 你这百万金臂的厉害
'cause I got a good idea about that five-cent head of yours.
不过我觉得你的大脑却毫不值钱
Hit 'im, man!
快投，伙计！
Fuck!
他妈的！
Ball four.
坏球
Who the fuck are you?
你是什么人？
Good punch.
好拳
I'm Crash Davis. I'm your new catcher...
我叫克拉舍戴维斯 是你的新接球手…
and you just got lesson number one:
你已经学会了第一课
Don't think.
不要多想
It can only hurt the ball club.
否则只会毁了俱乐部
Come inside, I'll buy you a drink.
进去吧，我请你喝一杯
He's my new catcher.
我的新接球手
We fight, she gets the clown. How's that happen?
我们在外面打架，她却玩的开心 这算是怎么回事？
God, I like this song.
我喜欢这首歌
Did you boys stop fightin'?
你们休战了？
Pals now?
现在成朋友了？
That's good.
那就好
I love a little macho male bonding.
我喜欢男子汉之间的友谊
I think it's sweet. I do.
我觉得这很可爱
Even if it probably is latent homosexuality being rechanneled.
尽管这有可能会发展为同性恋
I'm all for rechanneling, so who cares, right?
可我还会将之扭转过来， 谁在乎呢，对吗？
Okay, shall we go to my place?
好了，去我家吗？
Which one of us?
要我们哪个去？
Both of you, of course.
当然是你们两个一起来
These are the ground rules.
基本的规则就是这样
I hook up with one guy a season.
每赛季我都会和个男人在一起
Usually takes me a couple weeks to pick the guy.
通常我会花两星期去挑人
Kind of my own spring training.
来做我个人春季特训的人选
You two are the most promising prospects of the season so far.
你们二位是本赛季最有希望的
I just thought we should kinda get to know each other.
我觉得我们该互相认识下
Time-out. Why do you get to choose?
暂停，为什么要由你来选择？
- Why? - Why do you get to choose?
-什么？ -为什么要由你来选择？
Why don't I get to choose? Why doesn't he get to choose?
为什么不是由我来选择？ 或是为什么不由他来选择？
Actually, nobody on this planet ever really chooses each other.
事实上，这世界上的关系 不是在互相选择
It's all a question of quantum physics...
量子物理学就已经解释过
molecular attraction and timing.
分子是互相吸引的
Laws we don't understand that bring us together and tear us apart.
我们并不理解左右我们 相距分离的法则
It's like pheromones.
那就象是外激素的作用
You get three ants together, they can't do dick.
要是把三只蚂蚁摆在一块， 它们不会繁衍
You get 300 million of them, they can build a cathedral.
但若是把三亿只聚在一起， 它们会造出大教堂
Is somebody gonna go to bed with somebody?
还有人想上床吗？
Honey, you are a regular nuclear meltdown.
亲爱的，你就象是座快喷发的火山
You better cool off.
最好先冷却一下
Where you going?
你去哪儿？
After 12 years in the minor leagues, I don't try out.
在联赛中我已经混了12年， 不需要再受什么训练
Besides...
此外…
I don't believe in quantum physics when it comes to matters of the heart.
我不信用量子物理学 能解释思想上的问题
What do you believe in, then?
那你信什么？
I believe in the soul...
我信仰灵魂…
the cock, the pussy...
那些单纯的性交…
the small of a woman's back...
那些女人的小气…
the hanging curveball, high-fiver, good scotch...
曲线变化球，鼓掌欢呼…
that the novels of Susan Sontag are self-indulgent, overrated crap.
苏珊桑塔格的小说中说的是放纵
I believe Lee Harvey Oswald acted alone.
我信仰刺杀肯尼迪的人 是被指使的说法
I believe there oughta be a constitutional amendment...
我信仰宪法会对球场上的烂草皮
outlawing Astroturf and the designated hitter.
和指定代打的规则做出修改
I believe in the sweet spot, soft-core pornography...
我信仰最佳击球点和有节制的色情
open your presents Christmas morning rather than Christmas Eve...
选择在圣诞的清晨打开礼物 要比在平安夜打开好
and I believe in long, slow, deep, soft, wet kisses...
我还信仰那种悠长深远，柔软温馨的吻
that last three days.
能够让人亲上三天三夜
Good night.
晚安
Oh, my.
天啊
Hey, what's all this molecule stuff?
这些分子什么的是什么意思？
Crash, wait!
克拉舍，等等！
All's I want is a date.
我只是想要度过段时间
I'm not gonna fall in love with you or nothing.
我没想和你谈恋爱或是怎么的
I'm not interested in a woman who's interested in that boy.
我对那种只喜欢小毛孩的女人没兴趣
Good night.
晚安
- I'm not interested yet. - Who you calling a boy?
-我还没发生兴趣呢 -你说的小毛孩是指谁？
See you at the yard, Meat.
球场见，废人
Damn, nobody's ever said no to a date with me before.
没人以前这么拒绝过我
He's crazy.
他有病
I want you bad.
我想和你做坏事
Honey, hold on. Slow down.
亲爱的，等等，慢点来
I wanna watch.
我想要看着你脱
Go ahead. Put it back on.
快，穿回去
Jesus, what kind of chick are you?
你这样的女人我从没见过
When you know how to make love, then you'll know how to pitch.
当你懂得如何做爱， 你自然会投出好球
I know how to pitch.
我知道该怎么投球
Good.
很好
Now take it off slowly.
慢慢的脱下衣服
That's nice.
这样子很好
Oh, my, what a nice back.
你的背真好看
Honey. Sweetheart.
亲爱的.甜心
Try taking off your shoes and socks first.
把袜子和鞋子也脱了
My socks? It's cold in here.
连袜子也要脱？这儿够冷的
What?
怎么了？
You think Dwight Gooden leaves his socks on?
你认为德特古登 也会不脱袜子就上床吗？
Ebby, honey.
艾比，亲爱的
Have you ever been tied up in bed?
有被绑在床上过吗？
Bring it on, baby!
这真好玩！
I heard about shit like this.
我听说过这玩意
You ever heard about Walt Whitman?
那你听说过沃特惠特曼吗？
Who's he play for?
他是干什么的？
He sort of pitches for the Cosmic All-Stars.
他就象是宇宙全明星赛的投球手
- Never heard of him. - Oh, good.
-从没听说过 -那好
Listen to this.
听听这个
"I sing the body electric.
"我为身体中的兴奋而歌唱
The armies of those I love engirth me and I engirth them.
我喜欢那感觉包围着我， 而我也包围着他们
They will not let me off till I go with them...
他们不会让我离去， 直到我跟随他们
respond to them and discorrupt them...
响应他们，与他们狂欢
and charge them full with the charge of the soul.
用灵魂的负荷去充满他们
But the expression of a well-made man appears not only in his face...
优雅男士的表情不只出现于脸上
it is in his limbs and joints also."
还在与他的四肢和关节"
Excuse me. Are we gonna fuck or what?
等等，我们还要不要做爱了？
"It is curiously in the joints of his hips and wrists.
"他臀部和腕部的关节尤为奇妙
Love flesh swelling and deliciously aching.
爱潮翻涌，伴随美妙的痛苦
Limitless limpid jets of love, hot and enormous."
爱的清泉喷涌而出，热烈而汹涌"
Listen up, guys. Can I have your attention a minute?
大伙听好了， 留神听我说几句话
I'm gonna be leading a daily chapel service here in the locker room...
我打算在下午三点在休息室
- at 3:00 in the afternoon. - Amen, brother!
-开始做次祈祷仪式 -阿门，兄弟！
Y'all are invited to stop on by and worship before batting practice.
欢迎你们在练习赛开始前 和我一起做些祈祷
Jimmy, goddamn it. Loosen up and get laid.
吉米，放松些
I know y'all think I'm pretty square, but...
我知道你们都会觉得我古板…
I believe what I believe.
可我有自己的信仰
Jesus, Ebby, you look like a truck ran over you.
天，艾比，你就象被卡车轧过一样
Nuke. Call me Nuke.
"纽克"，叫我"纽克"
Annie says it's my new nickname.
这是安妮新给我起的绰号
Okay, Nuke. Go get 'em.
好吧，纽克.好好干
Annie nailed you? Annie did?
安妮挑上你了？是吗？
That's great. That means you're gonna have a great year.
那不错，意味这你今年会很顺
Is she as good as they say?
她就和他们说的那样棒吗？
No, man, we didn't fuck.
别说了，我们根本没有搞
No, she read poetry to me all night.
她对我念了整晚的诗
It's more tiring than fucking.
这可比做爱累多了
"Limpid jets of love."
"爱的清泉喷涌而出"
Hey, Crash. Does that mean what I think it means?
克拉舍，这话的意思 和我想的该是一样吧？
"Limpid jets of love."
"爱的清泉喷涌而出"
Your shower shoes have fungus on them.
你的拖鞋上都已经发霉了
You'll never make it to the bigs with fungus on your shower shoes.
要这个样子你永远成不了什么大器
Think classy, you'll be classy.
思想优雅，举止也会优雅
If you win 20 in the Show...
要是你能在表演赛中赢20场…
you can let the fungus grow back on your shower shoes...
你大可以继续让你的拖鞋发霉…
and the press will think you're colorful.
而记者们会认为你很有个性
Until you win 20 in the Show, however...
但不管你怎么厉害…
means you're a slob.
这总说明你是个懒人
Y'all don't forget Saturday is Bull Day...
大家都记得周末是公牛日
down at the Northgate Mall.
都来到了北门街
Strike!
出局！
Whoa, too bad, Butch.
太糟了，大老粗
Charge!
真差！
Not getting that cheese by me, Meat.
别以为我那么好对付，废物
And now batting for the Bulls, number eight, Crash Davis.
现在出场的击球手 是8号克拉舍戴维斯
Foul ball!
界外球！
God, stupid fuck, Crash.
真蠢，克拉舍
What'd you swing at a breaking ball for?
你怎么以为他会投出曲线变化球？
Fuck me.
真该死
You usually start me off with a hammer.
你总是先要给我点打击
You're thinking too much, Crash. Get out of your fuckin'head.
你想的太多了，克拉舍 保持清醒
Don't let him in your kitchen.
别让怪想法来捣乱
Come on, Crash. Just relax. You got it, honey.
加油，克拉舍 放松，你行的
All right, here we go. Stay back. Relax.
好了，上吧 稳住，放松
Quick bat.
快击！
Foul ball!
界外球！
Throw that shit again, Meat. Throw that weak-ass shit again.
有种再扔一次，废人 有本事就再扔那种烂球
Okay, get close. You got it. One more, baby.
集中注意力，你行的
He's gonna throw the deuce now.
这次他该还我个球了
He's gotta waste one.
他想浪费掉这球
Stay back and wipe that silly grin off his face.
看他站在那里傻笑就知道了
Come on. Bring it.
来吧，给我
Jesus Christ!
天啊
What the hell was that?
那算是什么？
What goes around, comes around.
怎么了，清醒点
Son of a bitch throws hard.
混蛋才投的那么重
It's okay, Crash. You take it easy, honey.
没事的，克拉舍 放松些，亲爱的
All right, one and two. You can eat this shit. Relax.
好了，一，二 吃屎去吧，轻松点
Annie.
安妮
Who's this Annie?
谁是安妮
Jesus, get out of the box, idiot. Where's your head?
别胡思乱想了，白痴 你的脑袋是怎么了
Get the broad outta your head!
把这女人从你脑子里赶出去！
Time-out!
暂停！
Give me a rag.
把布给我
Get a hit, Crash.
击个好球，克拉舍
Shut up.
闭嘴
All right, you've seen all his pitches.
好了，你已经看到他是怎么投的
You've seen them all.
你已经摸清了他的球路
Shorten up, Crash. Bring me the gas, kid.
干净利落点，克拉舍 给我个好球，孩子
Quick bat.
快击
Strike!
出局！
Scotty, baby, take this to Crash.
斯科特，好孩子，把这交给克拉舍
Folks, we have a little lost girl up here.
大家注意，这儿有位迷路的小女孩
Says her name is Lana Ann Baker.
她的名字是兰娜安贝克
- She'll be waiting... - It's for Crash.
-她会在… -给克拉舍的
at the ticket box for her daddy, Cedar Baker.
检票处等她的父亲，席德贝克
Cedar, come get your little girl.
席德，快去领你的女儿
- What? - From Annie.
-怎么？ -安妮给你的
Read it.
念出来
"Dear Crash, you have a lovely swing...
"亲爱的克拉舍，你的转身很漂亮…
but you're pulling your hips out too early.
可是挥杆的时间过早了
I'd be happy to meet you tomorrow at the batting cage to discuss it.
我很乐意明天在练球场 能与你讨论一下
Signed, Annie."
安妮"
If there's one chick who'd know you were pulling your hips out early...
要是有哪个女人能指出 你的挥杆的时间过早
it'd be Annie.
那一定是安妮
It's kind of a personal note, kid, so don't read it.
上面有些私人话题，所以别看
There you go.
给你
Here, Millie.
给你，米莉
What's it say?
他怎么说？
It says, "I wanna make love to you. Crash."
上面写着， "我想和你做爱.克拉舍"
Oh, my.
天啊
See my hips?
注意我的腰部了吗？
Yep.
是的
And I think Susan Sontag is brilliant.
我觉得苏珊桑塔格很了不起
Is this gonna happen? Us?
那这关系也能在我俩间发生吗？
I'm committed to Nuke for the season.
这赛季我要忠于纽克
Oh.
噢
You had your chance the other day.
你会有机会的
What is it you see in this guy?
你看好这家伙哪点？
He's a young, wild...
他是个年轻，莽撞…
dim, pretty boy.
愚笨的漂亮小子
Young men are uncomplicated.
年轻人总是很单纯
And he's not dim. He's just inexperienced.
而且他并不傻，他只是缺乏经验
It's my job to give him life wisdom...
我的任务就是教给他些人生的智慧
and help him get on to the major leagues.
帮助他闯进大联盟
That's funny, that's my job too.
真有趣，那也是我的职责所在
Damn!
该死！
You're pulling your hips.
你的屁股找不到方向
I know, but they're nice hips.
我知道，可它们是漂亮的屁股
I looked up your records.
我查到了你的记录
You what?
什么？
You hit 227 home runs in the minors.
你在小型联赛中 打出过227个本垒打
That's not bad.
那挺不错
Don't tell anybody.
别去和别人说
Why not? You hit 20 more this year...
为什么？今年你就 已经击出了20多个
you're gonna be the all-time minor-league champ.
你就快破了小型联赛的本垒打记录
The record's 246.
记录是246打
Well, 247 home runs in the minor leagues...
小型联赛中的本垒打记录
would be a kind of dubious honor.
并不值得炫耀
I think it would be great. The Sporting News should know it.
可我觉得那很棒， 也该知道
No. Just no. Please.
不，请不要.拜托
Okay.
好吧
Last chance, your place or mine?
最后问你一次，去你家还是我家？
Despite my rejection of most Judeo-Christian ethics...
尽管我拒绝接受宗教上 那种关于道德的思想
I am, within the framework of the baseball season, monogamous.
可我还是不会在一个赛季中 找第二个男人的
- Gimme a break. - It's true.
-慢点说 -这是实话
Stop it.
别这样
Jeez, the fact is...
事实是…
you're afraid of meeting a guy like me, 'cause it might be real...
你在怕遇上我这样的人， 会把这关系弄假成真
so you sabotage it with some, what is it...
所以就找出些借口来
bullshit about commitment to a young boy you can boss around.
胡扯些关于你要对 这个随你指挥的孩子负责的话
That's a great deal.
那是个好借口
Nice.
很好
I know women like you.
我了解象你这样的女人
You're a regular patron saint.
你是个可靠的守护神
Stray cats, lost causes...
专门保护那些无主的小猫， 迷路的可怜人
or 6'3" homeless studs.
或是六尺三寸高的种马
Oh, Crash, you do make speeches.
克拉舍，你真会说话
Crash, that was fabulous.
克拉舍，你太棒了
Crash?
克拉舍？
You mean Nuke. You said Crash.
你想说纽克，却叫出克拉舍来
No, I said Nuke.
不，我说的就是纽克
Oh, no.
哦，不是的
Sweetie, you shouldn't listen to what a woman says...
亲爱的，你不该把女人在
when she's in the throes of passion.
高潮时候说的话记在心里
They say the darndest things.
她们说的都是讨厌的东西
Yeah, you said Crash.
是的，你说了克拉舍
Honey...
亲爱的…
would you rather I'd be making love to him using your name...
那你觉的我和他 做爱时喊你的名字好
or making love to you using his name?
还是和你做爱时喊他的名字好？
Yeah, maybe you're right.
也许你说的对
Welcome to the Eastern Seaboard Tobacco Growers...
欢迎观看东区烟草杯
City Council Little League Cash Drop Day.
城市棒球小型联赛
These young fellas... young men, I should say... over here to my left.
这些好小子们-- 已经站到了我的左边
Hi, 18. Hi, 12.
嗨，18号 嗨，12号
Hey, Dino.
嗨，迪诺
Hey, Millie.
嗨，米莉
Hey. I'm Millie.
嗨，我叫米莉
I'm married.
我已经结婚了
What is that?
那是什么玩意？
Chicken bone cross.
鸡骨十字架
Takes the curse off the bat that brings me hits.
那能下咒使我击出好球
What are you, a goddamn witch?
这是巫术吗？
Yes, a switch-hitting witch.
对，是安打巫术
Will that work for me?
对我也有用吗？
If you believe in voodoo.
除非你信仰伏都教
Jose, I am zero for 16.
乔斯，我已经被三振16次
A big fucking doughnut hole for 16.
连续16次得到大零蛋
I can't remember the last time I had a base hit.
几乎都不记得上次安打 是什么时候的事了
Let me have some of that stuff.
让我也沾点光吧
That is not belief. That's desperation.
你那样不是获得信心， 你是走投无路
Jose, come on. Just touch my bat once.
乔斯，拜托了， 就碰下我的球棒吧
Come on, just once. I won't bother you the rest of the day.
只碰一下就行了 我保证今天都不会来烦你了
I swear to God. Just touch the bat once.
我对天发誓，碰一下就行
Ladies and gentlemen, five, four...
女士们，先生们， ，         …
three, two, one.
，
Let it go!
放！
One thousand big ones!
一千张大票！
That batter ain't nothin'. Come on, Nuke.
那个击球手菜的很， 加油.纽克
Cut it!
短球！
Time-out.
暂停
Let's play ball!
好好打球！
Stay there. Give me the ball.
别动，把球给我
Hey.
嘿
Relax, all right?
放松点好吗？
Don't try to strike everybody out.
不要老想把人三振出局
Strikeouts are boring. Besides that, they're fascist.
三振出局使人心烦， 而且也太独裁了
Throw some ground balls.
投些基础球吧
More democratic.
民主些
What's this guy know, anyway?
这家伙知道个屁
If he's so great, how come he's been in the minors for ten years?
要是他真那么了不起 怎么还是老窝在小型联赛中混不出去？
If he's so hot, how come Annie wants me instead of him?
要是他真那么厉害， 安妮怎么会选我而不是他？
And another thing, Meat, you don't know shit.
还有件事，废物， 你什么都不会
You wanna make it to the Show, you'll listen to me.
要是想打出漂亮的球， 那就好好听我的
Annie only wants you 'cause she can boss you around. Got it?
安妮选你是因为 她能支配你，明白吗？
Relax. Let's have some fun out here.
轻松点，让我们干的漂亮点
This game's fun.
这项运动是很有意思的
Fun, goddamn it.
很有意思
And don't hold the ball so hard.
别把球捏得那么紧
It's an egg. Hold it like an egg.
把这看成是鸡蛋，要象捏鸡蛋一样
What's he know about fun? I'm young. I know about fun.
他知道什么？ 我年轻，我知道什么是乐趣
Old man, he don't know nothin' about fun.
象他那样的老头根本不懂什么是乐趣
Nobody's goin' out there.
大家就位
Why's he calling for a curveball?
为什么他要我投曲线球？
I wanna bring heat.
我想要投高速球
Shake him off. Throw what you want.
别去管他的，按自己想法投
Goddamn it. Time-out.
该死的，暂停
Hey, why you shaking me off?
干什么不理我？
I wanna bring the heater. Announce my presence with authority.
我想要投高速球， 以宣告我在球场上的权威
- To announce what? - Announce my presence with authority.
-宣告什么？ -宣告我在球场上的权威
"Announce your presence with authority"?
"宣告你在球场上的权威"？
This guy's a fastball hitter, looking for heat.
这家伙擅长的就是击快球， 等着你的高速球
So what. He ain't seen my heat.
是吗？他还没见识过我的高速球
All right, Meat. Give him your heat.
好吧，废物，投你的高速球去吧
Why does he always call me Meat?
为什么他总是叫我废物？
I'm the guy driving a Porsche.
我才是风光人物
Fastball.
快球
Come on, Nuke. Settle down. Take your time.
来吧，纽克.镇定点 干个漂亮的
Home run for Bud Shelton of the Fayetteville Generals.
费耶特维尔将军队的 巴德谢尔顿本垒打
What are you doing standing here? I gave you a gift.
你傻站在这儿干什么？ 我送了你份大礼
You stand here showing up my pitcher? Run, dummy!
你还傻站着对投球手 耀武扬威？快跑，木头人
Give me the ball.
把球给我
He really hit the shit out of that one, didn't he?
他真的打出了好球，不是吗？
Held it like an egg.
捏球要象捏鸡蛋
And he scrambled the son of a bitch. He hit the fuckin' bull.
他让这杂种手忙却乱了， 他击中了那球
Guy gets a free steak.
那家伙算是搞到了免费的牛排
You havin' fun yet?
你还觉得有趣吗？
Oh, yeah, I've havin' a blast.
是啊，我快要气炸了
Good.
很好
Sucker teed off on that like he knew I was gonna throw a fastball.
他就好象早知道我要扔快球似的
- He did know. - How?
-他当然知道 -什么？
I told him.
是我告诉他的
One down now!
现在落后一球！
Come on, Nuke. You're the man. No batter. Chuck hard, baby.
加油，纽克.都看你的了
Don't think, just throw.
不要有杂念，只管投球
Strike!
出局！
God, that was beautiful. What did I do?
漂亮极了，我是怎么办到的？
Hang on, Millie. Here we go again.
继续，米莉 又回到老样子了
That's the first home run of the year for Crash Davis.
那是克拉舍戴维斯 今年击出的首个本垒打
That brings the score to Fayetteville 14, Durham 2.
现在场上比分是费耶特维尔队14分 达勒姆队2分
Hell of a shot.
打的好球
Sorry it got wasted.
只可惜将那浪费了
I don't know what to do with these guys.
我不知道该拿这些家伙怎么办
I beg. I plead. I try to be a nice guy.
我求他们，取悦他们 我尽量想做个好人
I'm a nice guy.
我本来就是个好人
They're kids. Scare 'em.
都是些小毛孩， 吓吓他们就行了
That's what I'd do.
我就是这么干的
Yeah.
对啊
Everybody into the shower!
所有人都给我站到水龙头下面去！
Anybody ain't in this shower in ten seconds gonna get fined $ 100.
要是谁十秒中之内还没过去 就会被罚100元！
- Larry. - One Mississippi...
-拉里 -一秒
two Mississippi, three Mississippi...
两秒，三秒
- four Mississippi. - Get in there! Hurry it up!
-四秒… -进来！快点！
seven Mississippi, eight Mississippi...
七秒，八秒
nine Mississippi, ten Mississippi.
九秒，十秒
You guys, you lollygag the ball around the infield.
你们在球场上浪费了无数的球
You lollygag your way down to first.
你们从比赛开始就找不到方向
You lollygag in and out of the dugout.
你们就只会在休息席混时间
You know what that makes you? Larry.
你们知道那使你们成了什么？ 拉里
Lollygaggers.
毫无价值的人
- What's our record, Larry? - Eight and sixteen.
-我们比分是多少，拉里？ -八胜十六负
Eight and sixteen.
八胜十六负
How'd we ever win eight?
我们该怎么赢回那八场？
It's a miracle.
只有奇迹才能实现
This is a simple game.
这是很简单的运动
You throw the ball.
只需要好好投球
You hit the ball.
好好击球
You catch the ball.
好好接球
You got it!
明白了没有！
We have got a 12-day road trip...
从明天起我们要开始…
starting tomorrow.
为期12天的巡回比赛
Bus leaves 6:00 in the morning.
明早六点出发
Goddamn, son of a bitchin', motherfuckin' shithead. Goddamn it!
该死的混蛋， 全都脑子里进了水！
Yeah, Skipper, you wanted to see me?
领队，你找我？
Yeah, Bobby. Shut the door.
是的，波比，把门关上
This the toughest job a manager has.
做球队的管理员并不容易
But the organization has decided to make a change.
但是球队必须做些调整
They're releasing you from your contract.
他们决定终止你的合同
Skip, I know I'm in a goddamn slump, but I hit the ball hard today.
领队，我知道最近我状态不好 可我今天真有打的很努力
Couple flares drop in for me, I'm right back in the groove.
只要给我几天时间， 我会回到最佳状态的
Sorry.
对不起
Let's go. Come on.
上车了，来吧
Nuke, honey!
纽克，亲爱的！
Let's go. We got five hours.
快上车了，只有五小时
Honey, I want you to wear these when you're pitching on the road.
亲爱的，我想你在路上 的时候能穿着这个
- What are they? - They're garters.
-这是什么？ -是我的吊袜带
They're gonna hug your waist and snuggle...
那会使你的精神更集中
and dangle off your thighs and buns in such a wonderful way.
动作也更灵敏
It'll help you see things differently.
帮助你对事物有不同看法
Plus, it'll remind you of me, which is a lot nicer...
还有，这会提醒你想起我， 想那些美好的时光
than thinking about all those nasty hitters.
而不会老是想起那些臭球
Jesus, Annie, I don't know.
安妮，我不明白
You've been pitching on the wrong side of your brain.
关于投球的想法你老是错误
This will help put things on the right side.
这会帮助你将那扭转过来
Big-league pitchers don't use these.
大联盟的球手们可不会用这玩意
They did when they were in the Carolina League.
可他们还在州联赛的时候就用
Nuke, excuse me. Time to go to work.
纽克，抱歉打扰 是时候该出发了
All right.
好吧
Bye, y'all.
大家再见
Gimme a break.
别来烦我
Go get 'em, boys! Hit 'em where they ain't.
打败他们，小伙子们 打的他们找不到方向
She may get woolly
她开始长毛
Young girls they do get woolly
年轻女孩她们都长毛
'Cause of all the stress
因为那压力
When they get woolly
当她们开始长毛
Try a little tenderness
那就试着温柔点
Stop it.
别唱了
Thank you.
谢谢
What?
干什么？
It's not "woolly."
不是"长毛"
Nobody gets "woolly." Women get "weary."
没有人会"长毛"， 女人们只会"乏味"
They don't get "woolly."
她们不"长毛"
Nobody's got "stress," they're wearing a "dress."
也不是"压力"， 她们是穿"衣服"
Damn, I hate people that get the words wrong.
我讨厌别人唱错词
How come you don't like me?
你为什么就这么不喜欢我？
You don't respect yourself, which is your problem.
你要是不尊敬自己， 那就是你自己的事
But you don't respect the game, and that's my problem.
但要是你不尊敬比赛， 那就关我的事
- You got a gift. - What do I got?
-你很有天赋 -我有什么？
You got a gift. When you were a baby, the gods reached down...
你很有天赋， 你出生的时候…
and turned your right arm into a thunderbolt.
上帝就给予了 你的右手雷电般的力量
You got a Hall-of-Fame arm, but you're pissing it away.
你有着能创造奇迹的手臂， 而你却将它糟蹋了
I ain't pissing nothing away. I got a Porsche already.
我根本没糟蹋什么， 大伙们都了解我的实力
I got a 9-11, with a quadraphonic Blaupunkt.
我投的很好，我是人们的话题人物
You don't need a quadraphonic Blaupunkt.
你不需要成为什么话题人物
What you need is a curveball.
你需要的是学会投曲线球
In the Show, everybody can hit a fastball.
比赛中谁都可以投出快球来
How would you know?
你知道什么？
You've been in the majors?
你在全国联赛打过吗？
Yeah, I've been in the majors.
对，我打过全国联赛
You were?
你有？
You've been in the Show?
你打过表演赛？
Yeah, I was in the Show.
是的
I was in the Show for 21 days once.
我曾打过21天的表演赛
Twenty-one greatest days of my life.
我这辈子最棒的21天
You never handle your luggage in the Show.
你根本不用自己拎行李箱
Somebody else carries your bags.
多的是有人来帮你提
It's great.
那真棒极了
You hit white balls for batting practice.
挥棒击球宣告比赛开场
Ballparks are like cathedrals.
球场就象是大教堂
The hotels all have room service.
宾馆永远有空房间
The women all have long legs and brains.
围着你的女人又聪明又漂亮
They're really hot?
她们都很热情吧？
Yeah, and so are the pitchers.
是的，面对的投手也是如此
They throw ungodly breaking stuff in the Show.
他们在球技上变化多端
Exploding sliders.
能投出爆炸般的外旋下坠球来
You could be one of those guys.
你也能和他们一样
Nuke could be one of those guys, but you don't give a fuck, Meat.
纽克本来也有这种实力， 可是他自甘堕落，废物
I am sick and fuckin' tired of you calling me Meat.
我受够了你叫我废物
You wanna step outside?
想到外面凉快凉快吗？
Yeah, I'll step outside.
好，我陪你凉快
What's the problem? What's happening?
怎么了？出什么事了？
I was just gonna ask Crash to show me how to throw a breaking ball.
我只是想叫克拉舍教我 该怎么投好曲线变化球
Good idea. Did anybody bring a ball?
好主意，谁给我拿个球来？
Double off the wall by Higgins.
希金斯击出左外野二垒打
Once again, Durham pitchers are unable to get the first out of the inning.
达勒姆队的投手再一次 浪费了场上的大好机会
The Bulls will attempt to end a six-game losing streak...
公牛队想要在对抗 格林斯博罗黄蜂队的比赛中
against the Greensboro Hornets with Nuke LaLoosh on the hill.
依靠纽克拉路什终止六连败
Base hit to center field off LaLoosh.
安打至中外场，拉路什失球
That closes the book on LaLoosh today.
统计下拉路什的成绩吧
Five earned runs, five hits, five strikeouts...
五次保送上垒， 五次安打，五次三振出局
five walks and five wild pitches.
五次自由上垒，五个场外球
It's time to tell it like it is, sports fans.
各位球迷，是时候该我这么说了
This is the most wretched road trip I've seen in 20 years.
这是我20年来所见过 最糟的巡回比赛
And possibly the worst Durham team in half a century.
也是半世纪来最差的达勒姆队
Is the modern-day athlete a pale imitation of the great warriors?
这些现代的年轻球员是在干什么？
Only Crash Davis stands out this year.
只有克拉舍戴维斯还过的去
Begging the question, what are these boys thinking about?
是时候该这些小伙子们好好想想了
'Cause it sure ain't baseball.
这根本不象是在打棒球
Hey, Mr. Hormone, check out this.
荷尔蒙先生，来看看这个
Ice-skaters. God, look at 'em.
是滑冰运动员，瞧瞧她们
Hey, fellas, that's what we need, man.
伙计们，那正是我们想要的
One night with these skaters, we can get right back on track.
和这些滑冰姑娘们共渡一夜 我们的状态就会全回复了
Yeah, right.
是啊
Just need a night off to end our losing streak.
只需要一个晚上 就能终止我们连败
What we need is a rain-out.
我们需要把这雨过天晴
I can get us a rain-out.
我能让大家雨过天晴
There ain't been a cloud in the sky in weeks.
已经连续一星期阴雨蒙蒙
Hundred bucks says I can get us a rain-out for tomorrow.
赌多少钱我能让 大家明天雨过天晴
You're on.
你输定了
I ain't paying for this. Crash, pay for this.
我不会为这付你钱的 克拉舍，你得付钱
Shut up. You're gonna wake everybody up.
闭嘴，不然会把别人吵醒的
Let the bonus baby pay for it.
让"胜利宝贝"来赔吧
Jesus, man.
天啊，伙计
Crash, what are you doing?
克拉舍，你在干什么？
Oh, my goodness!
天啊！
We got ourselves a natural disaster.
我们给自己人工制造自然灾害
Wake up.
醒醒
You're awake.
你已经醒了
You're okay.
没事了
You were dreaming.
只是在做梦
I was playing damn near naked.
我梦到自己几乎是全裸着在打球
- What? - I was naked.
-什么？ -我光着身子
Playing naked.
光着身子在打球
I know.
我明白
I know. I had that dream all the time too.
我也常做这梦
We're almost home.
快到家了
Watch your head.
小心头
Here you go. Let me get that back there.
给你，帮我拿到后头去
- I'm not your slave. - No, that one over there.
-我又不是你小弟 -不是，是那边那只
Hi.
嗨
God, I'm tired.
天，我累极了
What a trip.
这趟真够受的
I was lousy. I was worse than lousy.
我真没用，比没用还要糟糕
But every time I pitched, it was like throwing gasoline on a fire.
我每次投球的时候， 都象是将汽油撒到火里
I mean...
我的意思是--
What is all this I, I, I? What about me?
干嘛老是说"我，我，我"？ 怎么不问问我？
Aren't you glad to see me?
见到我不开心吗？
Don't I look nice?
我看来不好吗？
You look great. I'm sorry.
你看来好极了，对不起
I'm just totally exhausted.
我只是累极了
Good. Physical exhaustion can be spiritually fabulous.
很好，肉体上的疲倦 对精神上影响很大
What you need is a good game of catch.
你需要的是玩场接球游戏
Catch?
接球？
Baby, come on. Fire one in here.
宝贝，来吧，往这儿投
This is ridiculous. I'm a professional.
这太可笑了，我是专业球手
Will you just give it a try and lean in?
能不能先试了再说？
Thank you.
谢谢
I want you to breathe through your eyelids.
我现在要你用眼睛呼吸
My eyelids?
我的眼睛？
Like the lava lizards of the Galapagos Islands.
就象是加拉帕哥斯群岛 的火山蜥蜴一样
Some have a parietal eye behind their heads so they can see backwards.
它们的眼睛长在头顶， 所以能看见背后的环境
Haven't you ever noticed how Fernando Valenzuela...
你有注意过费尔南多范哲拉的投球吗
he just doesn't even look when he pitches?
他投球的时候目光是怎样的？
He's a Mayan Indian.
他是玛雅族土人出身
Or an Aztec. I forget which one. I get 'em confused.
或阿兹特克族.我也搞不清楚 我老把他们搞混
- So do I. - Stand up for a second.
-我也要这样 -站起来会
I want you to be aware of the chakra connection...
我想要你明白你的脚
between your feet and your testicles.
和皋丸之间存在的精神联系
- Chakra. - Your right leg and left testicle...
-精神中心 -你右脚和左皋丸有关